>> Jem Young: 好的，谁让他们的机器人工作?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: All right,
who got their chatbot working?
我们必须采取一些步骤，这似乎是不寻常的。
There were some steps we had to go
through that would have seemed unusual.
我们都是在 NGINX 之外的某个地方做的。
We did them all already at some
point other than the NGINX portion.
我们都做了，但要记住这一点是很难的，因为你学到了很多，
We did them all, but it's hard to remember
this because you've learned many,
很多小时的知识
many hours of knowledge.
你已经学会了 Kubernetes 到 TCP。
And you've learned Kubernetes to TCP.
我们在任何地方都学会了
We've learned everywhere in between.
所以当它回到实际编程的时候
So when it comes back down
to actual programming,
有点容易被绊倒了
it's a little easy to get tripped up.
所以我们来看看我们是怎么把这个
So let's walk through exactly
how we hook this up and
我们如何将网络套接字连接到我们的网站上
how we hooked up web
sockets to our website.
希望你们中有一些人创造了一些有趣的回应。
Hopefully, some of you created
some funny chatbot responses.
我没有把握机会，但我有一些好的想法。
I didn't quite get the chance,
but I had some good ideas.
也许我稍后会在 Git 存储库中实现它们，或者可以自由地打开采购申请。
Maybe I'll implement them in the Git
repo later, or feel free to open a PR.
所以我们想做的第一件事， > > Jem Young:
So the first thing we wanna do,
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
我要回我的堡垒历史来告诉你我做了什么
I'm just gonna roll back through my
bash history to show you what I did.
>> Jem Young: 我第一次做的是备份到 /var/www 目录。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: The first thing I did was
I backed up to the /var/www directory.
我运行了 git 克隆，所以我将整个存储库复制到这个 var 目录中。
And I ran git clone, so I cloned that
entire repo to this var directory.
当你克隆某些东西时，它会自动为你创建一个文件夹。
And when you clone something, it's gonna
automatically create a folder for you.
那个文件夹是满满的
And that folder was full stack,
前端 v2 ，所以 fsfev2。
front end v2, so fsfev2.
从那里，我要把它转至那个目录，所以请使用 cd fsfev2。
And from there, I'm gonna cd into
that directory, so cd fsfev2.
快跑我们看起来很好
Run ls, we're looking good.
然后我就跑了一个 npm 的安装，就是要保证里面有所有的包，
Then I ran a npm install, just to make
sure I have all the packages in there,
应该是最新的好的
should be up-to-date, cool.
但现在我有两个节点应用程序在同一个服务器上运行
But now I have two node applications
running on the same server,
或者在同一个端口上。
or on the same port.
所以我想杀了另一个申请的人我现在不需要了
So I wanna kill the other application,
cuz I don't need it for now.
所以我要杀了他
So I'm gonna kill that.
所以我要说 sudo pm2
So I'm gonna say, sudo pm2.
第一个进程在进程 0。
And the first process was at process 0.
我们只跑了一个
We only had one running.
所以我们要停止 0
So we're gonna stop 0.
但是，因为我已经在进程 0 中运行了，所以我要再次停止它。
But because I already have it running in
the process 0, I'm gonna stop it again.
我们可以走了很酷
We're good to go, cool.
所以现在 0 站
So now 0 stops.
我要运行 sudo pm2， >> Jem Young: 启动，
I'm gonna run sudo pm2,
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: start,
我们要去另一个申请了
we're gonna run this other application.
但我已经做过了我不想再开始了
But I've already ran it,
I don't wanna start another process, but
您将运行 sudo pm2 启动 app.js。
you would run sudo pm2 start app.js.
所以现在我们停止了另一个应用程序另一个在运行
So now we've stopped the other
application, the other one's running,
你可以走了
you're good to go.
不幸的是，我们仍然需要通过 NGINX 隧道连接。
Unfortunately, we still need to tunnel
the web socket connection through NGINX.
>> Jem Young: 我们用这个，哎呀，我们去吧。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So we use this,
oops, there we go.
我们必须在 NGINX中设置这些代理升级头。
We have to set those proxy
upgrade headers in NGINX.
所以在我们的 NGINX 配置中， >> Jem Young: In
So in our NGINX configuration,
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: In
我们的定位块在 proxy_pass 的上方或下方
our location block,
right above the proxy_pass, or below it,
不重要的是我们设置了代理标题
it doesn't really matter,
we set a proxy header.
我们要设置升级头。
We wanna set up an upgrade header.
然后，我们要为连接升级设置另一头。
And then we wanna set a another header for
connection upgrade.
>> Jem Young: 那么远吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Pretty good so far?
> > Jem Young: 我会给你第二个例子。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I'll give
you a second just in case.
这很有打字的
It's a lot of typing.
>> Jem Young: 你的手可能已经被伤害了。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Your hands
are probably hurting by now.
你用过指挥线路也许比你在生活中所使用的时间还多
You've used the command line maybe more
than you've ever used in your life, and
那就好
that's good.
好，当我们修改 NGINX 配置时，我们要做什么 ?
Okay, so when we modify our NGINX
configuration, what do we have to do?
一二三重启对
One, two, three, restart, yes.
所以我们重新加载我们的 NGINX ，我只是经历了我的历史，我很懒，
So we reload our NGINX, and I'm just
going through my history, cuz I am lazy,
sudo 服务 nginx 重新装入。
sudo service nginx reload.
>> Jem Young: 其中一个可能是缺少的步骤。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: One of these was
probably the missing step.
如果你不按顺序来做，或者不一定要按顺序来做，
And if you don't do them in order,
or not necessarily in order,
但你不会得到每一个的申请你的申请就不起作用了
but you don't get every single one of
them, your application won't work.
因此，这一点，我们有一个新的应用程序在同一个端口上运行。
So this point, we have a new
application running on the same port.
如果有 Web 站点连接，那么它将执行升级，并且它应该工作。
If there's a website connection, it's
gonna do an upgrade, and it should work.
现在如果你去你的网站我要去我的
So now if you go to your website,
I'm gonna go to mine.
看我的插座已经启动了它在运行我可以打个招呼
See that my socket is up and
it's running, I can say hello, and
它的回报很棒因为我没有以任何方式修改剧本
it returns awesome because I didn't
modify that script in any way.
现在如果你想修改剧本的话
Now, if you wanted to modify the script,
if you wanna look exactly where that
生机立命，大一点， >> Jem Young: 是
chatbot lives, make that a little bigger,
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: It's
就在这个 handleQuery中
just in this handleQuery.
您将在此处为每个查询编写一个交换机语句。
You would write a switch
statement here for every query.
所以如果我说这个查询是，你好，写一个开关。
So if I said the query was,
hello, write a switch.
在这种情况下，你可以向大家问好。
In that case, for hello,
you can return hello.
你可以返回任何你想要的东西
You can return whatever you want.
你可以说现在是什么时候
You can say what time it is.
您可以抓取系统时间。
You can grab the system time.
如果你想变得复杂和抓取一个系统的载荷
If you wanna get complicated and
grab, say, a system load, like,
我的服务器怎么样了你可以这样回答
how's my server doing,
you could respond like that.
这是真实的机器人吗
Is this a real chatbot?
我不知道我不知道
I don't know.
我不相信任何的閒话
I don't in believe in chatbots anyways.
但如果你想建立一个，这就是你如何做到的。
But if you wanted to build one,
this is how you do it.
当我布局步骤时，希望它们对您有意义。
When I layout the steps,
hopefully they make sense to you.
我们必须采取的所有步骤，才能到达我们今天的位置。
All the steps we had to do to
get to where we are today.
它以 Git的某些技巧为基础，修改了我们的联系，
And it's kinda built on some of the skills
using Git, modifying our connection,
添加页眉之类的内容。
adding headers, things like that.
但只有简单的事情才能让你得到，除非你一再重复
But it's the simple things that can get
you, and unless you do them repeatedly,
很难记住确切的步骤
it's hard to remember the exact steps.
所以，如果你第一次没有得到它，就不要感到难过了。
So if you didn't get it the first time,
don't feel bad at all.